http://www.advertisingiq.com/privacy-policy

Ad.IQ Privacy Policy
Get Started
Select one...
Analytics
Thank you! Your submission has been received. Our Customer Service team will be getting in contact with you soon.
Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.
Services
BrandingWebsite DevelopmentSocial MediaBrand ManagementTalent ManagementBusiness LoansAnalyticsVoice SearchVideo Marketing
Learn
Claim Your BusinessMicro Moments
PricingReviewsSuccess StoriesBlogAd.IQ CaresBusiness Resource HubLoginGet Started
Privacy Policy
This is the Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") of Ad.IQ ("Ad.IQ" or "us" or "we"). Ad.IQ is committed to maintaining privacy protections for its users. Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine our on-line advertising services and sale of merchant vouchers (the "Services") with integrity in dealing with our users and merchants. The Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and store the personal information you provide to us. Our Terms of Service, which incorporates by reference this Privacy Policy, governs your use of our online services, any content or information therein, the Ad.IQ website at www.Ad.IQ.com, any subdomains of www.Ad.IQ.com, and any other website pages on which services are provided by us (collectively, the "Site").
INFORMATION WE COLLECT
HOW WE USE AND SHARE INFORMATION
HOW WE PROTECT INFORMATION
YOUR RIGHTS REGARDING THE USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
INTERNATIONAL USERS
CONTACT US
---------------------------------
INFORMATION WE COLLECT
We collect "Non-Personal Information" and "Personal Information." Non-Personal Information includes information that cannot be used to personally identify you, such as anonymous usage data, general demographic information we may collect, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, preferences you submit and preferences that are generated based on the data you submit and number of clicks. Personal Information includes information that can be linked to a specific individual, such as a name and/or your business' name, address, telephone number, email address, payment information and other information which you submit to us at the Site. Sharing Personal Information with us is entirely optional.
1. Information collected via Technology
In an effort to improve the quality of the Site and the Services, we track information provided to us by your browser when you view the Site or use the Services, such as your Internet service provider, the website you came from (known as the "referring URL"), the type of browser you use, your operating system, the device from which you connected to the Services, the time and date of access, the Site pages viewed, time spent at our Site, the sites visited just before and just after our Site, and other information that does not personally identify you. We track this information using cookies, or small text files which include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are a feature of web browser (Internet Explorer, Firefox, etc.) software that allows web servers to recognize the computer used to access a site. They are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's web browser on one site to simplify subsequent interactions with that site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transaction on related web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from site to site and to complete transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized.
Cookies are sent to a user's browser from our servers and are stored on the user's computer hard drive. Sending a cookie to a user's browser enables us to collect Non-Personal information about that user and keep a record of the user's preferences when utilizing our services, both on an individual and aggregate basis. For example, Ad.IQ may use cookies to collect the following information:
Website visits
Name
E-mail address
Ad.IQ may use both persistent and session cookies; persistent cookies remain on your computer after you close your session and until you delete them, while session cookies expire when you close your browser.
If you do not wish to transmit cookie information about yourself, you may turn off the cookie function in your web browser; please consult the "Help" section of your web browser to correctly do so. If you elect to turn off cookies, however, you may not be able to access certain features of the Site and your use of some portions of the Site may be affected.
Third Party Cookies
The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, and service providers is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, and service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.
Web beacons
Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.
Widgets
Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button . These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.
2. Information you provide us by using the Site or Services
In addition to the information provided automatically by your browser when you visit the Site, you may choose to provide us with personally identifiable information in connection with your visit to the Site or use of the Services, such as your email address, name and your business' name, payment information and postal address. You may also submit information in connection with vouchers, including merchant, business or service name, location, offer descriptions, product names, store information, discounts, conditions of offers, restrictions and exclusions of offers, expiration date, or any other content relating to offers or promotions. If you purchase merchant vouchers via the Site, you may be required to provide sensitive billing information including credit card information and billing address. To use elements of the Services you may need to create a merchant profile. You can create a profile by registering directly through the Site and entering your email address, and creating a user name and a password. By registering, you are authorizing us to collect, store and use your email address in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
No Use of Our Site by Persons under 13
The Site is not intended for use by anyone under 18, except with the explicit permission and under the supervision of a parent or guardian who accepts full legal responsibility for the minor's use. No person under 13 should disclose information on this Site. Ad.IQ doesn't knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a child under 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us at the email address provided below to remove the information and opt out of promotional opportunities. You may learn more about protecting children's privacy online by visiting www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy.
HOW WE USE AND SHARE INFORMATION
Personal Information
Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, trade, rent or otherwise share for marketing purposes your Personal Information with third parties without your consent. We do share Personal Information with vendors who are performing services for Ad.IQ, such as third party payment processors, advertisers of your content and service providers who send communications to you on behalf of Ad.IQ. Those vendors use your Personal Information only at our direction and in accordance with our Privacy Policy.
In order to provide the Services to our merchant clients, including marketing, promoting and selling offers and vouchers on behalf of such clients, we may share any Personal Information you submit to the Site in connection with your purchase or interest in a particular merchant's offer or voucher with such merchant in order for such merchant to more effectively provide or promote its products or services to you. Such merchant's use of your Personal Information is subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy
In general, the Personal Information you provide to us is used to help us communicate with you. For example, we use Personal Information to contact users in connection with the provision of Services to users, in response to questions, solicit feedback from users, provide technical support, and inform users about promotional offers.
Non-Personal Information
In general, we use Non-Personal Information to help us improve the Services and customize the user experience. We use Non-Personal Information to provide the Services, including the creation and marking of vouchers. We also may aggregate Non-Personal Information in order to track trends and analyze use patterns on the Site. This Privacy Policy does not limit in any way our use or disclosure of Non-Personal Information and we reserve the right to use and disclose such Non-Personal Information to our partners, advertisers and other third parties at our discretion.
Blog
We maintain a Ad.IQ blog, available at blog.Ad.IQ.com, to provide our users and clients with information about our Services and related marking trends. If you post to the blog, you should be aware that any Personal Information submitted can be read, collected or used by any person who visits the blog. We are not responsible for Personal Information or any other information you chose to submit to this forum. To request removal of your personal information from our blog contact us at support@ad.iq. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.
If you choose to comment on posts in the blog through Twitter and/or Facebook, we do not receive access to your Personal Information from those sites. Comments to our blog may not contain spam or profanity and should be related to topics and posts contained on the blog. We reserve the right to moderate any user-submitted comments and to edit or remove any comments that do not meet these guidelines. We reserve the right to use, reproduce and share user or client submitted comments in any form.
Mergers,Acquisitions and Similar Business Transactions
In the event we undergo a business transaction such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Personal Information as well as Non-Personal Information may be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge and consent that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any acquirer of our assets may continue to process your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If our information practices change at any time in the future, we will post the policy changes to the Site so that you may opt out of the new information practices. We suggest that you check the Site periodically if you are concerned about how your information is used.
Sharing Information with the Government or As Otherwise Required by Law
We may also use or disclose information collected on the Site to resolve disputes or investigate problems. We may disclose or access such information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it such as to comply with a subpoena, or if we consider it necessary to maintain the Services and improve our products and services.
HOW WE PROTECT INFORMATION
We implement security measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure or accidental loss or destruction of Non-Personal Information and Personal Information, including credit card information. We further protect your information from potential security breaches by implementing certain technological security measures including encryption, firewalls and secure socket layer technology. However, these measures do not guarantee that your information will not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software. Although we take reasonable steps to safeguard and prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information, we can't be responsible for the acts of those who gain unauthorized access, and we make no warranty, express, implied or otherwise, that we will prevent such access. By using visiting our Site and using our Services, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks. Communications you may have with us via email or U.S. Mail may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures are in place prio r to your sending information. Therefore, if you choose to communicate with us through these means, you are assuming the risk of doing so and we request that you do not send or post sensitive information through these means.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
As part of the Services, we may provide links to or compatibility with other websites or applications. Some of these sites may even be co-branded with the Ad.IQ name or logo. However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by those websites or the information or content they contain. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us through the Site and the Services. Therefore, this Privacy Policy does not apply to your use of a third party website accessed by selecting a link on our Site or via our Services. The privacy policy of that other website or application will apply to your access or use of that site or application. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of other websites before proceeding to use them.
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
Please read the Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy carefully. Ad.IQ reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. We will notify you of significant materialchanges to our Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on our Site. Significant changes will go into effect 30 days following such notification. Non-material changes or clarifications will take effect immediately. You should periodically check the Site and this privacy page for updates. The effective date of the latest version of the Privacy Policy will appear on this page.
INTERNATIONAL USERS
This Site is hosted and operated in the United States of America. Those who access or use the Site or the Services from other jurisdictions do so at their own choice and risk and are solely responsible for compliance with local law. Please note that the personal information you submit to our Site will be transferred to and stored in the United States to be processed by us so we can provide this Site and the Services to you as set forth in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service.
If you are not a resident of the United States, you acknowledge and agree that we may collect and use your personal information outside your home jurisdiction, and that we may store your personal information in the United States. Please note that the level of legal protection provided in the United States or other non-European countries in which you may access our Site or use the Services may not be as stringent as that under European Union privacy standards or the privacy laws of some other countries, possibly including your home jurisdiction.
CONTACT US
If you desire not to receive information about products or services we think may be of interest to you or if you wish to access, delete or correct you information, please send us an email to legal@ad.iq.
If you no longer wish to receive promotional offers or communications from us, you may follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in the email communications you receive or you may contact us at support@ad.iq.
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of this Site, please contact us by sending an email to legal@ad.iq.
Data Retention
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at support@ad.iq. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
California law permits visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us at legal@ad.iq.
HomeTermsPrivacy
© 2020 Ad.IQ All Rights Reserved.
Ad.IQ, a Social Media Growth and Brand Management Agency, charges management fees for features and benefits associated with the free services by our Marketing Partners. All Marketing Partners' marks are the property of their respective owners.
Facebook
Twitter
Instagram
LinkedIn
Youtube
Podcast
